<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DrukINFO</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation__main">Districts</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rateus_activity">Rateus_activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us_">About_us_Activity</string>
    <string name="aboutUs_content">Kinzang Pelden \n Kishan Gurung \n Megnath Gurung \n Sonam Choki</string>
    <string name="aboutUs_content1">Any kind of enqueries and feedbacks are welcomed at drukinfo@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- main content of festival-->
    <string name="thimphu_festival">Thimphu Tshechu \n\n
        The annual national holiday is held for three consecutive days, beginning on 10th day of the 8th month of lunar calendar.
        The history of Thimphu Tshechu began in 1867, when it was initiated by the 4th Desi, Gyalse Tenzin Rabgay. During its first
        years, the tshechu only features a few dances, performed by monks only. Thimphu Tshechu however was never the same again in
        the 1950, under the third King of Bhutan, Jigme Dorji Wangchuk added colors and variations to the festival with a number of
        masked dances performed by monks called Boed chhams. Despite the changes, the religious core of the festival is still kept intact.
        The most famous dances during Thimphu Tshechu are Shaw Shachi (Dance of the Stags) and Guru Tshengye (Eight Manifestations of Guru). \n\n
        Start Date: Sep 19, 2018 \n End Date: Sep 21, 2018 \n Destination: Thimphu Dzong \n
        Thimphu Drupchen \n\n
        Thimphu Drupchen or Drubchen (popularly known as Thimphu Dromchoey) is performed at the Thimphu Tashichhodzong. The sacred masked dance is dedicated
        to appeasing the protecting deity of Bhutan, Pelden Lhamo. The dance ceremony was instituted between 1705 and 1709 by Kuenga Gyaltshen, the first
        reincarnation of Jampel Dorji, son of Zhabdrung Ngawang Namgyal. According to legend, Pelden Lhamo appeared before him and performed the dances while
        he was in meditation. Based on these dances, Kuenga Gyeltshen initiated the dance ceremony. Thimphu Drubchen is a 5 day event preceding the popular
        3 day Thimphu Tsechu festival. Because it is mainly to appease the protecting deities, it is considered more sacred and was not open for tourists until recently.
        Photographing may be prohibited during the Drubchen. \n\n
         Start Date: Sep 15, 2018 \n End Date: Sep 15, 2018 \n Destination: Thimphu Dzong \n
    </string>

    <string name="paro_festival">Paro Tshechu \n\n The Paro Tshechu is one of the biggest festivals in the country. On the first day, all mask dances are held
        inside the courtyard of the Dzong. In the subsequent days, the courtyard outside the dzong hosts the festival.Paro Tsechu is one of the most popular
        festivals in Bhutan. Featuring dances performed by trained monks and laymen in amazing masks and costumes, Tsechus (festivals) are one of the best ways
        to experience the ancient living culture of Bhutan. A Tsechu is a Buddhist festival in honour of Guru Rimpoche, the saint who brought Buddhism to Bhutan.
        A highlight of the Paro Tsechu is the unfurling of the silk Thangka – so large it covers the face of an entire building and is considered one of the most
        sacred blessings in the whole of Bhutan. The ‘Thangka, known in Bhutan as a ‘thongdroel’ is a religious picture scroll, and is only exhibited for a few
        hours at daybreak on the final day of the festival enabling the people to obtain its blessing. This holy scroll “confers liberation by the mere sight of
        it” (the meaning of the word ‘thongdroel’ in Bhutanese). This tour also takes advantage of the beautiful spring time growth with stunning hikes through
        the countryside to a Rhododendron forest in Phobjikha, as well as a visit to the Lamperi a Rhododendron Festival near Dochu La Pass. The sacred sites of Paro,
        Thimphu and Punakha are also featured. \n\n
        Start Date: March 27, 2018 \n End Date: March 31, 2018 \n Destination: Paro Dzong
    </string>
    <string name="punakha_festival">
        Punakha Drubchen \n\n
        In the 17th century, Zhabdrung Ngawang Namgyal of Punakha in western Bhutan defeated the invading Tibetan forces
        which led to the unification of the country as one nation. To honor this victory, a grand celebration, the Punakha Drubchen (a.k.a. Puna Drubchen),
        was held. It went on to become an annual festival of the district. Expectedly, the major part of the festival is a theatrical reenactment of
        the epic battle. The battle scenes are performed by the local militia men (pazaps) dressed in the battle gear of those ancient times. This highlights
        the fact that during that period there was no national army as such, and the battle was fought by young men from the eight village blocks (tschogchens)
        of Thimphu who came forward voluntarily to do battle with the enemy. \n
        In 2005, the locals put forward a request to the 70th Je Khenpo, Trulku Jigme Choedra, and the government that they wanted another similarly grand
        festival which would help in keeping tradition alive besides, of course, further commemorating the great deeds of Zhabdrung Rimpoche. Accordingly,
        the Punakha Tshechu was introduced in the district as one more annual event. It should also be noted that Punakha is also where the Chief Abbott
        (Je Khenpo) of Bhutan has his winter residence. \n

         During the time of the festivals (Punakha Drubchen: March 6-March 10; and Punakha Tshechu: March 11-March 13) would be pretty worthwhile
        for any tourist as they will have the opportunity to get a good glimpse of ancient Bhutanese history along with its culture and traditions.
        The venue for the festivals is a walled fortress known as Punkaha Dzong which is situated at the confluence of two rivers and has some impressive temples
        and large courtyards inside.  So, what say? If you are ready and raring to go, here’s one itinerary that will allow you to attend the opening and closing
        days of the festivals and, in between, you get to see some other interesting places. \n\n
            Start Date: Feb 21, 2018 \n End Date: Feb 24, 2018 \n Destination: Punakha Dzong \n \n

        Punakha Tshechu \n\n
        The Punakha Tshechu is one of the most popular tshechu in country. It is held right after Punakha Drubchen. \n\n
        Start Date: Feb 25, 2018 \n End Date: Feb 27, 2018 \n Destination: Punakha Dzong \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="haa_festival">Total population 138,736 \n Male  : 72,522 \n Female : 66,214 \n\n
         THIMPHU THROMDE Total population 114,551 \n Male  : 58,996 \n Female : 55,555 \n\n
        OTHER THAN THROMDE Total population 24,185 \n Male  : 13,526 \n Female : 10,659
    </string>


    <!-- main content of festival-->
    <string name="thimphu_population">Total population 138,736 \n Male  : 72,522 \n Female : 66,214 \n\n
         THIMPHU THROMDE Total population 114,551 \n Male  : 58,996 \n Female : 55,555 \n\n
        OTHER THAN THROMDE Total population 24,185 \n Male  : 13,526 \n Female : 10,659
    </string>
    <string name="paro_population">Total population 46,316 \n Male  : 23,941 \n Female : 22375</string>
    <string name="punakha_population">Total population 28,740 \n Male  : 15,079 \n Female : 13,661</string>
    <string name="haa_population">Total population 13,655 \n Male  : 7,435 \n Female : 6,220</string>
    <string name="gasa_population">Total population 3,952 \n Male  : 2,104 \n Female : 1,848</string>
    <string name="wangdiphodrang_population">Total population 42,186 \n Male  : 24,302 \n Female : 17,884</string>
    <string name="chukha_population">Total population 68,966 \n Male  : 36,041 \n Female : 32,925 \n\n
            PHUNTSHOLING THROMDE Total population 27,658 \n Male  : 15,052 \n Female : 12,606 \n\n
        OTHER THAN THROMDE Total population 41,308 \n Male  : 20,989 \n Female : 20,319

    </string>
    <string name="dagana_population">Total population 24,965 \n Male  : 12,956 \n Female : 12,009</string>
    <string name="samtse_population">Total population 62,590 \n Male  : 32,022 \n Female : 30,568</string>
    <string name="sarpang_population">Total population 46,004 \n Male  : 24,018 \n Female : 21,986</string>
    <string name="pemagatshel_population">Total population 23,632 \n Male  : 11,922 \n Female : 11,710</string>
    <string name="zhemgang_population">Total population 17,763 \n Male  : 9,165 \n Female : 8,568</string>
    <string name="samdrupjongkher_population">Total population 35,079 \n Male  : 18,329 \n Female : 16,750 \n\n
        SAMDRUP JONGKHER THROMDE Total population 9,325 \n Male  : 5,016 \n Female : 4,309 \n\n
        OTHER THAN THROMDE Total population 25,754 \n Male  : 13,313 \n Female : 12,441</string>
    <string name="tashiyangtse_population">Total population 17,300 \n Male  : 8,719 \n Female : 8,581</string>
    <string name="tashigang_population">Total population 45,518 \n Male  : 23,414 \n Female : 22,104</string>
    <string name="lhuntse_population">Total population 14,437 \n Male  : 7,407 \n Female : 7,030</string>
    <string name="trongsa_population">Total population 19,960 \n Male  : 11,878 \n Female : 8,082</string>
    <string name="bumthang_population">Total population 17,820 \n Male  : 9,396 \n Female : 8,424</string>
    <string name="mongar_population">Total population 37,150 \n Male  : 18,247 \n Female : 18,903 </string>
    <string name="tsirang_population">Total population 22,376 \n Male  : 11,526 \n Female : 10,850</string>


</resources>
