<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DrukINFO</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation__main">Districts</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="title_activity_rateus_activity">Rateus_activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us_">About_us_Activity</string>
    <string name="aboutUs_content">Kinzang Pelden \n Kishan Gurung \n Megnath Gurung \n Sonam Choki</string>
    <string name="aboutUs_content1">Any kind of enqueries and feedbacks are welcomed at drukinfo@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- main content of festival-->
    <string name="thimphu_festival">Thimphu Tshechu \n\n
        The annual national holiday is held for three consecutive days, beginning on 10th day of the 8th month of lunar calendar.
        The history of Thimphu Tshechu began in 1867, when it was initiated by the 4th Desi, Gyalse Tenzin Rabgay. During its first
        years, the tshechu only features a few dances, performed by monks only. Thimphu Tshechu however was never the same again in
        the 1950, under the third King of Bhutan, Jigme Dorji Wangchuk added colors and variations to the festival with a number of
        masked dances performed by monks called Boed chhams. Despite the changes, the religious core of the festival is still kept intact.
        The most famous dances during Thimphu Tshechu are Shaw Shachi (Dance of the Stags) and Guru Tshengye (Eight Manifestations of Guru). \n\n
        Start Date: Sep 19, 2018 \n End Date: Sep 21, 2018 \n Destination: Thimphu Dzong \n
        Thimphu Drupchen \n\n
        Thimphu Drupchen or Drubchen (popularly known as Thimphu Dromchoey) is performed at the Thimphu Tashichhodzong. The sacred masked dance is dedicated
        to appeasing the protecting deity of Bhutan, Pelden Lhamo. The dance ceremony was instituted between 1705 and 1709 by Kuenga Gyaltshen, the first
        reincarnation of Jampel Dorji, son of Zhabdrung Ngawang Namgyal. According to legend, Pelden Lhamo appeared before him and performed the dances while
        he was in meditation. Based on these dances, Kuenga Gyeltshen initiated the dance ceremony. Thimphu Drubchen is a 5 day event preceding the popular
        3 day Thimphu Tsechu festival. Because it is mainly to appease the protecting deities, it is considered more sacred and was not open for tourists until recently.
        Photographing may be prohibited during the Drubchen. \n\n
         Start Date: Sep 15, 2018 \n End Date: Sep 15, 2018 \n Destination: Thimphu Dzong \n
    </string>

    <string name="paro_festival">Paro Tshechu \n\n The Paro Tshechu is one of the biggest festivals in the country. On the first day, all mask dances are held
        inside the courtyard of the Dzong. In the subsequent days, the courtyard outside the dzong hosts the festival.Paro Tsechu is one of the most popular
        festivals in Bhutan. Featuring dances performed by trained monks and laymen in amazing masks and costumes, Tsechus (festivals) are one of the best ways
        to experience the ancient living culture of Bhutan. A Tsechu is a Buddhist festival in honour of Guru Rimpoche, the saint who brought Buddhism to Bhutan.
        A highlight of the Paro Tsechu is the unfurling of the silk Thangka – so large it covers the face of an entire building and is considered one of the most
        sacred blessings in the whole of Bhutan. The Thangka, known in Bhutan as a ‘thongdroel’ is a religious picture scroll, and is only exhibited for a few
        hours at daybreak on the final day of the festival enabling the people to obtain its blessing. This holy scroll confers liberation by the mere sight of
        it (the meaning of the word thongdroel in Bhutanese). This tour also takes advantage of the beautiful spring time growth with stunning hikes through
        the countryside to a Rhododendron forest in Phobjikha, as well as a visit to the Lamperi a Rhododendron Festival near Dochu La Pass. The sacred sites of Paro,
        Thimphu and Punakha are also featured. \n\n
        Start Date: March 27, 2018 \n End Date: March 31, 2018 \n Destination: Paro Dzong
    </string>
    <string name="punakha_festival">
        Punakha Drubchen \n\n
        In the 17th century, Zhabdrung Ngawang Namgyal of Punakha in western Bhutan defeated the invading Tibetan forces
        which led to the unification of the country as one nation. To honor this victory, a grand celebration, the Punakha Drubchen (a.k.a. Puna Drubchen),
        was held. It went on to become an annual festival of the district. Expectedly, the major part of the festival is a theatrical reenactment of
        the epic battle. The battle scenes are performed by the local militia men (pazaps) dressed in the battle gear of those ancient times. This highlights
        the fact that during that period there was no national army as such, and the battle was fought by young men from the eight village blocks (tschogchens)
        of Thimphu who came forward voluntarily to do battle with the enemy. \n
        In 2005, the locals put forward a request to the 70th Je Khenpo, Trulku Jigme Choedra, and the government that they wanted another similarly grand
        festival which would help in keeping tradition alive besides, of course, further commemorating the great deeds of Zhabdrung Rimpoche. Accordingly,
        the Punakha Tshechu was introduced in the district as one more annual event. It should also be noted that Punakha is also where the Chief Abbott
        (Je Khenpo) of Bhutan has his winter residence. \n

         During the time of the festivals (Punakha Drubchen: March 6-March 10; and Punakha Tshechu: March 11-March 13) would be pretty worthwhile
        for any tourist as they will have the opportunity to get a good glimpse of ancient Bhutanese history along with its culture and traditions.
        The venue for the festivals is a walled fortress known as Punkaha Dzong which is situated at the confluence of two rivers and has some impressive temples
        and large courtyards inside.  So, what say? If you are ready and raring to go, here one itinerary that will allow you to attend the opening and closing
        days of the festivals and, in between, you get to see some other interesting places. \n\n
            Start Date: Feb 21, 2018 \n End Date: Feb 24, 2018 \n Destination: Punakha Dzong \n \n

        Punakha Tshechu \n\n
        The Punakha Tshechu is one of the most popular tshechu in country. It is held right after Punakha Drubchen. \n\n
        Start Date: Feb 25, 2018 \n End Date: Feb 27, 2018 \n Destination: Punakha Dzong \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="haa_festival">Haa Summer Festival \n\n The Haa summer festival is a lively and uplifting celebration of traditional living-culture, nomadic lifestyles, unique Bhutanese
        cuisine, traditional sports and religious performances. It provides unparalleled insight into the lives and traditions of Bhutan’s nomadic herders.
        It displays a lively traditional living culture, nomadic life styles, demonstration of local cuisines, brewing of local ara, traditional sports,
        religious performances, dances, songs, artifacts and natural alpine flowers. \n
         Annual Haa Tshechu is underway at the lower courtyard of Lhakhang Karpo on the eighth and ninth day of the eighth lunar month. The three-day festival showcases various
        mask dances namely Shazam and Zhana Chams. Hundreds of people draped in their best attires gathered to witness the dzongkhag’s biggest festival. The Tshechu will end on Saturday
        with the unfurling of Guru Nangsi Zilon Thongdrel for public veneration at Wangchuk Lo Dzong. It was introduced in 1990 to honour Guru Padmasambhava. \n\n
        Start Date: July 14, 2018 \n End Date: July 15, 2018 \n Destination: Town festival Ground, Haa \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="gasa_festival">Gasa Tshechu \n\n  The Gasa festival (tshechu) is the biggest festival in the small district of Gasa in northwest Bhutan. Gasa is home to highlander communities.
        While many mask dances are performed,the local folk dances performed are very unique and distinct adding to the festive mood of the celebration. \n Festival provides the occasions for the
        community to get together, By witnessing the festivals, our sins are removed and blessed with virtues and merits. Family members are gathered together during the festivals.
         Explore how these religious dances convey religious messages to the people. Discover how it brings joy and happiness to all sentient beings. It is also a time, where the Bhutanese will
        dress up with their finest traditional dresses. Festivals play a very important role in the essence of Bhutanese culture. Festivals are combination of both the spiritual and social.
         Festival teaches the basic precepts of Buddhism to the people. Mingle and be like local and happy people of Bhutan. Explore, Discover and enjoy the religious festivals held in the
        Himalayan Kingdom of Bhutan.\n\n
        Start Date: March 24, 2018 \n End Date: March 26, 2018 \n Destination: Gasa Dzong \n \n

        Bum Tashi Festival \n\n The Bum Tashi festival of Gasa has been named after the region’s protecting deity Tashi Thongoen. It basically involves making offerings and prayers to
        this protecting deity. \n\n
        Start Date: Sep 16, 2018 \n End Date: Sep 16, 2018 \n Destination: Gasa Dzong \n \n
        Royal Highland Festival \n\n
        first Royal Highland Festival and pioneering Laya Run was being organised in 2016 (a pilot and precursor for the forthcoming Snowman Run). Spearheaded by the Gasa Dzongdag,
        the historic event was inspired by the vision and passion of His Majesty Jigme Khesar Namgyal Wangchuck, the Fifth King of Bhutan, under the initiative: A Good to Great Gasa.
        Perched high on the festival grounds above the main town, the Royal Highland Festival highlights the richness and spirituality of Layap culture and traditions, including clothing,
        dance, music, handicrafts, food, sports, games, livestock and pastoralist practices. The highlight of the festival was meeting His Majesty The Fifth King, who graced the
        historical inauguration of the first-ever Royal Highland Festival, as well as the following year. As festival goers sang and danced around massive bonfires that sent bright
        sparks floating into the crisp Himalayan night under a glittering star-studded night sky, I could not help but pinch myself. What a special place. What an awesome night. \n\n
         Start Date: August 25, 2018 \n End Date: August 25, 2018 \n Destination: Dzong \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="wangdi_festival">Wangdue Phodrang Tshechu \n\n The annual Wangdiphodrang Tshechu was introduced by Zhabdrung Ngawang Namgyal after the completion of the Dzong.
         The festival is held in Wangduephodrang and is observed for three days in the autumn season. The Tshechu is well known
        for the Raksha Mangcham or the dance of the Ox. Many different kinds of mask dances are performed during the festival. It concludes with the unfurling of the Guru Tshengye Thongdrol. \n\n
        Start Date: Sep 17, 2018 \n End Date: Sep 19, 2018 \n Destination: Tencholing Army Ground, Wangdue \n
    </string>

    <string name="trongsa_festival">Trongsa Tshechu \n\n The Trongsa tshechu one of the oldest tshechus in Bhutan. It is believed that tshechus in other parts of Bhutan was spread from Trongsa Dzongkhag.
        All the chams/dances are just like regular tshechu of other Dzongkhags (Rang lug gi Cham). On the last day, a Thongdrol is unfurled.The Lhamoi Dromche is an annual festival performed by
        the monks of Trongsa Dzongkhag. The chams/dances include many forms worshipping the female guardian deity (Mahakali) of Bhutan.\n This festival bring together people from all walks of life and
        falls sometime in the month of December. In addition to traditional mask dances, visitors can witness the unfurling of the sacred Thongdrol and receive blessings from high ranking monks.
        People also receive blessings from the sacred Nangtens that is opened during the last day of the Tshechu.\n
        Start Date: Feb 20, 2018 \n End Date: Feb 22, 2018 \n Destination: Trongsa Dzong \n
    </string>
    <string name="bumthang_festival">Bumthang Tshechu \n\n According to legend, the concept of Tsechu was instituted in Bhutan by Guru Padmasambhava, the great Nyingmapa scholar (the oldest of
        the four major schools of Tibetan Buddhism) when he first visited Bhutan and Tibet in the 8th and 9th Century. He visited Bhutan to heal the dying King Sindu Raja, the king of present
        Bumthang then. Padmasambhava performed series of dance of subjugation to conquer local deities and gods to restore king’s health and in return the King agreed to spread Buddhism in Bhutan. \n
        Guru Padmasambhava instituted the first Tshechu in Bumthang where the most popular and sacred of all the mask dances, Guru Tshengye or the eight manifestation of Guru Padmasambhava
        were presented through eight form of dances. Myth has it that Guru Padmasambhava manifested himself in eight different human forms and danced in front of a fearful demon that was hiding from
        Padmasambhava.  These became the Chams (dances) depicting glory of Padmasambhava after the fearful demon was transformed into a protector of Buddhism by him. \n
        There are other Chams (dances) presented in Tshechus also created by great scholars like Terton Pema Lingpa, Zhabdrung Rimpoche, Melirepa and other great saints. These Chams are believed
        to be seen enacted in the dreams in the realm of zangdopelri (Gurus Paradise) and then replicated on earth to the people and followers through Gurmas (songs)- Story of Sharop Gem Dorji,
        and fables – story of the Raksha Mangcham (judgment of the dead). \n
        Kurjey Tsechu \n\n
        Kurjey Tsechu is celebrated in the popular Kurjey Lakhang in Bumthang. People of Jakar and Kurjey villages attend the Tshechu to pay obeisance to Guru Rinpoche who brought Buddhism to Bhutan.
        It is a one-day festival and the chams/dances include the Guru Tshengye and Shinjay cham performed by the monks of Kurjey Lhakhang. It is then closed with unfurling of a giant Buddha/Guru
        Thangka painting known as thongdrel. The festival is fully supported and funded by the government of Bhutan. \n\n
        Start Date: June 23, 2018 \n End Date: June 23, 2018 \n Destination: Kurjey Lhakhang, Choekhor \n\n
        Tharpaling Thongdrol \n\n
        Tharpaling Thongdrol is a one day festival and is mainly the display of gaint thangka or thongdrol (applique silk work with buddhist images) of Jowo Jampa and Kuenkhen Longchen Rabjam
        which are displayed every year alternatively (15th day). The Thongdrol is preceded by prayer ceremonies called the Moelam Chenmo which is performed by the monks of Tharpaling Lhakhang
        for 10 days to the local people of Chumey every year (1st -14th day). No chams /dances are performed during the entire festival. \n\n
    Start Date: March 2, 2018 \n End Date: March 2, 2018 \n Destination: Tharpaling Lhakhang, Chumey \n\n
    </string>


    <!-- main content of population-->
    <string name="thimphu_population"> \n\n Thmphu Population \n\n The population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n  Total population 138,736 \n Male  : 72,522 \n Female : 66,214 \n\n
         THIMPHU THROMDE Total population 114,551 \n Male  : 58,996 \n Female : 55,555 \n\n
        OTHER THAN THROMDE Total population 24,185 \n Male  : 13,526 \n Female : 10,659 \n\n
        Dzongkha, or Bhutanese is a Sino-Tibetan language spoken by over half a million people in Bhutan;
        it is the sole official and national language of the Kingdom of Bhutan. The word dzongkha means the language of the district ; kha is language, and dzong is district. \n
        Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.


    </string>
    <string name="paro_population">\n\n Paro Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 46,316 \n Male  : 23,941 \n Female : 22375
    Dzongkha, or Bhutanese is a Sino-Tibetan language spoken by over half a million people in Bhutan;
        it is the sole official and national language of the Kingdom of Bhutan. The word dzongkha means the language of the district ; kha is language, and dzong is district. \n
        Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.
    </string>
    <string name="punakha_population">\n\n Punakha Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n  Total population 28,740 \n Male  : 15,079 \n Female : 13,661 \n\n Dzongkha, or Bhutanese is a Sino-Tibetan language spoken by over half a million people in Bhutan;
        it is the sole official and national language of the Kingdom of Bhutan. The word dzongkha means the language of the district ; kha is language, and dzong is district. \n
        Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.
    </string>
    <string name="haa_population">\n\n Haa Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n  Total population 13,655 \n Male  : 7,435 \n Female : 6,220 \n\n
    Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.
    </string>
    <string name="gasa_population">\n\n Gasa Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 3,952 \n Male  : 2,104 \n Female : 1,848 \n\n
    Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.
    </string>
    <string name="wangdiphodrang_population">\n\n Wangdi Phodrang Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 42,186 \n Male  : 24,302 \n Female : 17,884 \n\n
    Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.
    </string>
    <string name="chukha_population"> \n\n Chukha Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\nTotal population 68,966 \n Male  : 36,041 \n Female : 32,925 \n\n
            PHUNTSHOLING THROMDE Total population 27,658 \n Male  : 15,052 \n Female : 12,606 \n\n
        OTHER THAN THROMDE Total population 41,308 \n Male  : 20,989 \n Female : 20,319 \n\n
        Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.

    </string>
    <string name="dagana_population">\n\n Dagana Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n  Total population 24,965 \n Male  : 12,956 \n Female : 12,009 \n\n
    Language \n\n Dzongkha is the national language, as well as the lingua franca of Bhutan and the native language of
western Bhutan, comprising eight (Thimphu, Paro, Ha, Gasa, Chukha, Punakha, Wangduphodrang, and
Dagana) of the twenty districts in Bhutan. It has the maximum number of speakers (estimated 160000).
Dzongkha is also the only Tibeto-Burman language which has a written script, besides Lhotshamkha.
Literally, Dzongkha means the language of the fortresses.
    </string>


    <string name="samtse_population">\n\n Samtse Population \n\n The population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 62,590 \n Male  : 32,022 \n Female : 30,568 \n\n
    Language \n
Lhotshamkha (loconym or ameliorative term for Nepali), the only Indo-Aryan language in Bhutan, is the language of the Lhotsampas (loconym or ameliorative term for Nepali speaking Bhutanese in
southern Bhutan). In terms of the number of speakers, Lhotshamkha is next to Dzongkha, with 156000 speakers. Lhotshamkha is historically a newly arrived language in southern Bhutan. The greater part of
Lhotshamkha populace are originally from Nepal. Many of the Lhotshamkha speakers were Limbu, Rai,Tamang, Gurung or Magar by origin, but in the process of abandoning their ancestral homelands became linguistically and culturally assimilated to the dominant Indo-Aryan language and culture.

    </string>
    <string name="sarpang_population">\n\n Sarpang Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 46,004 \n Male  : 24,018 \n Female : 21,986 \n\n
     Language \n
Lhotshamkha (loconym or ameliorative term for Nepali), the only Indo-Aryan language in Bhutan, is the language of the Lhotsampas (loconym or ameliorative term for Nepali speaking Bhutanese in
southern Bhutan). In terms of the number of speakers, Lhotshamkha is next to Dzongkha, with 156000 speakers. Lhotshamkha is historically a newly arrived language in southern Bhutan. The greater part of
Lhotshamkha populace are originally from Nepal. Many of the Lhotshamkha speakers were Limbu, Rai, Tamang, Gurung or Magar by origin, but in the process of abandoning their ancestral
        homelands became linguistically and culturally assimilated to the dominant Indo-Aryan language and culture.
    </string>
    <string name="pemagatshel_population">\n\n PemaGatsgel Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 23,632 \n Male  : 11,922 \n Female : 11,710 \n\n
   Language \n
Tsangla is spoken predominantly in eastern Bhutan, where it is also known as Sharchop-kha, the language of the Sharchop, i.e. people living in the east. The number of speaker is estimated as 138000 (Van Driem,
1992). As the largest of the non-official languages of Bhutan, it serves as a lingua franca for several smaller language groups in the eastern half of the kingdom. Tsangla, literally meaning, ‘talk’ (Kezang Tshering,
personal communication) is spoken in Trashigang, Pemagatshel, Samdrupjongkhar, and Mongar districts. Tshangla is also spoken just across the border from eastern Bhutan in Arunachal Pradesh and Dirang
        in the Kameng region in India (Andvik , 1993)
    </string>
    <string name="zhemgang_population">\n\n Zhemgang Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 17,763 \n Male  : 9,165 \n Female : 8,568</string>
    <string name="samdrupjongkher_population">\n\n The population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the world´s total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 35,079 \n Male  : 18,329 \n Female : 16,750 \n\n
        SAMDRUP JONGKHER THROMDE Total population 9,325 \n Male  : 5,016 \n Female : 4,309 \n\n
        OTHER THAN THROMDE Total population 25,754 \n Male  : 13,313 \n Female : 12,441 \n\n
       Language \n
Tsangla is spoken predominantly in eastern Bhutan, where it is also known as Sharchop-kha, the language of the Sharchop, i.e. people living in the east. The number of speaker is estimated as 138000 (Van Driem,
1992). As the largest of the non-official languages of Bhutan, it serves as a lingua franca for several smaller language groups in the eastern half of the kingdom. Tsangla, literally meaning, ‘talk’ (Kezang Tshering,
personal communication) is spoken in Trashigang, Pemagatshel, Samdrupjongkhar, and Mongar districts. Tshangla is also spoken just across the border from eastern Bhutan in Arunachal Pradesh and Dirang
        in the Kameng region in India (Andvik , 1993)
    </string>
    <string name="tashiyangtse_population">\n\n TrashiYangtse Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 17,300 \n Male  : 8,719 \n Female : 8,581 \n\n
       Language \n
Tsangla is spoken predominantly in eastern Bhutan, where it is also known as Sharchop-kha, the language of the Sharchop, i.e. people living in the east. The number of speaker is estimated as 138000 (Van Driem,
1992). As the largest of the non-official languages of Bhutan, it serves as a lingua franca for several smaller language groups in the eastern half of the kingdom. Tsangla, literally meaning, ‘talk’ (Kezang Tshering,
personal communication) is spoken in Trashigang, Pemagatshel, Samdrupjongkhar, and Mongar districts. Tshangla is also spoken just across the border from eastern Bhutan in Arunachal Pradesh and Dirang
        in the Kameng region in India (Andvik , 1993)
    </string>
    <string name="tashigang_population">\n\n Trashigang Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 45,518 \n Male  : 23,414 \n Female : 22,104 \n\n
   Language \n
Tsangla is spoken predominantly in eastern Bhutan, where it is also known as Sharchop-kha, the language of the Sharchop, i.e. people living in the east. The number of speaker is estimated as 138000 (Van Driem,
1992). As the largest of the non-official languages of Bhutan, it serves as a lingua franca for several smaller language groups in the eastern half of the kingdom. Tsangla, literally meaning, ‘talk’ (Kezang Tshering,
personal communication) is spoken in Trashigang, Pemagatshel, Samdrupjongkhar, and Mongar districts. Tshangla is also spoken just across the border from eastern Bhutan in Arunachal Pradesh and Dirang
        in the Kameng region in India (Andvik , 1993) </string>

    <string name="lhuntse_population">\n\n Lhuntshe Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 14,437 \n Male  : 7,407 \n Female : 7,030 \n\n
    Language \n
        Cho-can-nga-cha-kha, spoken in Mongar and Lhuntse districts, is the most closely related language to Dzongkha. Though the language is generally called Cho-can-nga-cha-kha by outsiders, the speakers
prefer to call it by their various loconyms, Tsamangli-kha (the language of Tsamang and Tsakaling, both
are villages in Mongar district), and Kurmetpi-kha (the language of Kurmet, which is the Cho-can-nga-
cha-kha speaking area of Lhuntse district) (Van Dreiem, 1992). The speakers of Cho-can-nga-cha-kha
are called Matpa, meaning inhabitants of lower area. \n\n
Kurtoepkha (or Kurtobi Zhake) is spoken in Lhuntse district. In the south, the Kurtoeb speaking area
begins at the village of Tangmachu, south of which Cho-can-nga-cha-kha is spoken. The dialect of
Tangmachu differs somewhat from the rest of the language as it is spoken elsewhere in the district (Van
Driem, 1992).

    </string>

    <string name="trongsa_population">\n\n Trongsa Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 19,960 \n Male  : 11,878 \n Female : 8,082</string>

    <string name="bumthang_population">\n\n Bumthang Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 17,820 \n Male  : 9,396 \n Female : 8,424 \n\n
    Language \n
Bumthangkha is the language of Bumtap (people from Bumthang district). Van Driem identified four major dialects of Bumthangkha; the dialect of Ura, the dialect of Tang, the dialect of Chogor, and the
dialect of Chunmat. On the one hand, the language is not only similar to Tibetan language but is also heavily influenced by Tibetan language (Michailovsky Mazaudon, 1994), on the other, Bumthangkha
is so similar to Khengkha and Kurtoekha that these two languages could be considered as dialects of
Bumthangkha (Van Driem, 1992).

    </string>

    <string name="mongar_population">\n\n Mongar Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 37,150 \n Male  : 18,247 \n Female : 18,903 \n\n
       Language \n
Tsangla is spoken predominantly in eastern Bhutan, where it is also known as Sharchop-kha, the language of the Sharchop, i.e. people living in the east. The number of speaker is estimated as 138000 (Van Driem,
1992). As the largest of the non-official languages of Bhutan, it serves as a lingua franca for several smaller language groups in the eastern half of the kingdom. Tsangla, literally meaning, ‘talk’ (Kezang Tshering,
personal communication) is spoken in Trashigang, Pemagatshel, Samdrupjongkhar, and Mongar districts. Tshangla is also spoken just across the border from eastern Bhutan in Arunachal Pradesh and Dirang
        in the Kameng region in India (Andvik , 1993)
    </string>

    <string name="tsirang_population"> \n\n Tsirang Population \n\nThe population of Bhutan represents 0.01 percent of the worlds total population which arguably
        means that one person in every 9425 people on the planet is a resident of Bhutan. \n\n Total population 22,376 \n Male  : 11,526 \n Female : 10,850 \n\n
    Language \n
Lhotshamkha (loconym or ameliorative term for Nepali), the only Indo-Aryan language in Bhutan, is the language of the Lhotsampas (loconym or ameliorative term for Nepali speaking Bhutanese in
southern Bhutan). In terms of the number of speakers, Lhotshamkha is next to Dzongkha, with 156000 speakers. Lhotshamkha is historically a newly arrived language in southern Bhutan. The greater part of
Lhotshamkha populace are originally from Nepal. Many of the Lhotshamkha speakers were Limbu, Rai, Tamang, Gurung or Magar by origin, but in the process of abandoning their ancestral
        homelands became linguistically and culturally assimilated to the dominant Indo-Aryan language and culture.
    </string>

    <!-- Geographical details -->

    <string name="thimphu_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Thimphu \n\n
        Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
        three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
        central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
        in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutans highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
        (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
        country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
        Thimphu is situated in the constricted, linear valley of the Raidak River, which is also known as the Thimphu River (Thimpu Chuu).
        While the surrounding hills are in an altitudinal range of 2,000 to 3,800 metres (6,562–12,467 feet) (warm temperate climate
        between 2,000 to 3,000 metres (6,562–9,843 feet) and cold temperate zone between 3,000–3,800 metres (9,843–12,467 feet),
        the city itself has an altitude range varying between 2,248 metres (7,375 feet) and 2,648 metres (8,688 feet). \n It is these two
        variations in altitude and climate which determine the habitable zones and vegetation typology for the valley. The valley, however,
        is thinly-forested and is spread out to the north and west. At the southern end of the city, the Lungten Zampa bridge connects the
        east and west banks of the Wang Chuu which flows through the heart of city. \n\n
     o	The average annual temperature in Thimphu is 11.6 °C. \n o	About 1599 mm of precipitation falls annually. \n
o	Latitude: 27.2757° N \n o	Longitude: 89.3830° E \n o	Elevation above sea level: 2307 m = 7568 ft \n o  Thimphu being under temprate zone
        animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars, wild pigs and barking deer. \n




    </string>

    <string name="paro_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of  Paro\n\n
        Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
        three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
        central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
        in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutans highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
        (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
        country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
       o	The average annual temperature is 12.4°C in Paro. \n o	 In a year, the average rainfall is 1820 mm. \n o	Latitude: 27°25′49″ N \n
       o	Longitude: 89°24′48″ E \n o	 Elevation above sea level: 2266 m = 7434 ft \n o  Paro being under temprate zone
        animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars, wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="punakha_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of  Punakha\n\n
        Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
        three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
        central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
        in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
        (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
        country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
       o	The average annual temperature in Punakha is 18.2°C. \n o	In a year, the average rainfall is 3016 mm. \no  Latitude: 27.5921° N,\n
      o	Longitude: 89.8797° E \n  o  Punakha being under temprate zone
        animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars, wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>


    <string name="haa_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Haa \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average annual temperature in Haa is 0.3°C. \n
    o	In a year, the average rainfall is 416 mm. \n
    o	Latitude: 27.3862° N \n
    o  Longitude: 89.2776° E \n
    o  Haa being under  higher altitudes you will come across snow leopards, blue sheep, red pandas,
        takin, marmots and musk deer. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="gasa_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of  Gasa \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average annual temperature in Gasa is 10.3°C.  \n o	In a year, the average rainfall is 1093 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.8983° N \n  o	Longitude: 89.7310° E  \n o  gasa being under  higher altitudes you will come across
        snow leopards, blue sheep, red pandas, takin, marmots and musk deer. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="wangdi_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Wangdi Phodrang  \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average annual temperature in Wangdue Phodrang is 18.1°C. \n  o	In a year, the average rainfall is 3080 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.4879° N \n  o	Longitude: 89.8996° E \n o  Wangdi being under temprate zone
    animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars, wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="trongsa_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Trongsa  \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	In Trongsa, the average annual temperature is 14.0°C. \n  o	In a year, the average rainfall is 1956 mm. \n
         o	Latitude: 27.5002° N \n  o   Longitude: 90.5081° E \n
o  Trongsa being under temprate zone animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas,
        sambars, wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="bumthang_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Bumthang \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
   Jakar \n\n
o	The average annual temperature is 11.7°C. \n
o	The average annual rainfall is 1404 mm. \n
Zugne \n\n
•	The average annual temperature is 10.8°C. \n
•	In a year, the average rainfall is 1280 mm. \n
	Domkhar \n\n
o	The average annual temperature is 9.8°C. \n
o	The average annual rainfall is 1143 mm. \n
	Ura \n\n
o	The average annual temperature is 8.8°C. \n
o	The average annual rainfall is 973 mm. \n
    o	Latitude: 27.6418° N \n  o   Longitude: 90.6773° E \n
o  Bumthang being under  higher altitudes you will come across
        snow leopards, blue sheep, red pandas, takin, marmots and musk deer. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="chukha_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Chukha \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average annual temperature is 23.2°C in Phuntsholing. \n
o	In a year, the average rainfall is 4383 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.0784° N \n
o	Longitude: 89.4742° E \n
o  Chukha being under temprate zone animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars,
        wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="dagana_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Dagana \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average annual temperature is 16.8°C in Daga. \n
o	About 3114 mm of precipitation falls annually. \n
o	Latitude: 27.0323° N  \n
o	Longitude : 89.8879° E \n
o   Dagana  being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>

    <string name="lhuntse_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Lhuntse \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	In Lhuntse, the average annual temperature is 15.4°C. \n
o	In a year, the average rainfall is 1899 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.8265° N  \n
o	Longitude: 91.1353° E \n
o   Lhuntse being under temprate zone animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars,
        wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="mongar_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Mongar  \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
   o	In Mongar, the average annual temperature is 17.2°C. \n
o	About 2444 mm of precipitation falls annually. \n
o	Latitude: 27.2617° N \n
o	Longitude: 91.2891° E \n
o  Mongar being under temprate zone animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars,
        wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="pemagatshel_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Pemagatshel \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	In Pemagatsel, the average annual temperature is 15.0 °C. \n
o	The average annual rainfall is 2049 mm. \n
o	Latitude:  27.0024° N \n
o	Longitude: 91.3469° E \n
o   Pemagatshel  being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="samdrupjongkher_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of  Samdrup jongkher \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
   o	In Samdrup Jongkar, the average annual temperature is 23.8 °C. \n
o	About 2749 mm of precipitation falls annually. \n
o	Latitude:  26.8036° N \n
o	Longitude: 91.5039° E \n
o   Samdrup jongkher being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="samtse_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Samtse \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutan\s highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
   o	The temperature here averages 22.5 °C. \n
o	The rainfall here averages 3825 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.0292° N \n
o	Longitude: 89.0562° E\n
o   Samtse  being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="sarpang_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of  Sarpang \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutans highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average annual temperature in Sarpang is 22.7 °C. \n
o	In a year, the average rainfall is 3950 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 26.9373° N \n
o	Longitude: 90.4880° E \n
o   Dagana  being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="tashigang_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Tashigang \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutans highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	In Tashigang, the average annual temperature is 18.8 °C. \n
o	In a year, the average rainfall is 2496 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.3325° N \n
o	Longitude:  91.5523° E \n
o   Tashigang  being under temprate zone animals found are Leopards, gorals, gray langurs, Himalayan black bears, red pandas, sambars,
        wild pigs and barking deer. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="tsirang_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Tsirang \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutans highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
   o	The average annual temperature in Damphu is 19.7 °C. \n
o	The rainfall here averages 3719 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.0322° N \n
o	Longitude:  90.1870° E \n
o   Tsirang being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="tashiyangtse_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Tashiyangtse \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutans highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average temperature in Trashiyangtse is 15.9 °C. \n
o	Precipitation here averages 1883 mm. \n
o	Latitude: 27.6825° N \n
o	Longitude: 91.4821° E\n
o  Tashiyangtse  being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="zhemgang_geographical"> \n \n Geographical Detail of Zhemgang \n\n
    Bhutan is a rugged land of steep mountains and deep valleys, that is easily divided into
    three main geographical areas. \n The lowlands front its southern border with India; the lesser (or lower) Himalayas cover the
    central areas, and its northern border with China is dominated by the massive peaks of the Himalayas. \n Many mountain peaks
    in northern Bhutan reach heights of over 7,000 meters. Bhutans highest point is Kula Kamgri which reaches a height of 24,783 ft.
    (7,554 m). \n Numerous small rivers drain the land, including the Dangme, Mangde, Sankosh and Torsa. The lowest point of the
    country is the Drangme Chhu river at 318 ft. (97 m). \n\n
    o	The average annual temperature is 16.8 °C in Daga. \n
o	About 3114 mm of precipitation falls annually. \n
o	Latitude: 27.0770° N  \n
o	Longitude : 90.8294° E \n
o   Dagana  being under tropical forests in the south are a haven for clouded leopards, elephants, one horned Rhinoceros, water buffalos, golden langurs, gaurs,
        swamp deer, hog deer, horn bills and many other species. \n\n
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_tourist_hotspot">tourist_hotspot</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

</resources>
